ÇAĞLAR TURKURKA

JAVA SOFTWARE ARCHITECT



caglarturkurka@gmail.com



+90 532 586 32 06



caalarturkurka



Diyarbakır, Turkey



https://www.linkedin.com/in/caglarturkurka



https://stackoverflow.com/users/885823/caglarturkurka



https://github.com/caglarturkurka



About Me



I was born July 24,1988 in Diyarbakır, Turkey. I completed primary and high school education in Diyarbakır, Turkey. I started to study in Computer Engineering at Izmır University of Economics and graudated with 3.25 degrees in 2011. In 2012, I got married and I have a child. I am developing Java Applications since 2006. I like to follow latest trends in Software Developing and try to be part of them. I am a fan of JHipster project and I follow it closely.

SKILLS



PERFECTIONIST COLLABORATIVE FRIENDLY

PIONEER MULTI TASKING PATIENT

SOFTWARE SKILLS

ANGULAR TYPESCRIPT SPRING SPRING BOOT **HIBERNATE** Node.js Socket.io **BOOTSTRAP 4** HTML 5 **DOCKER SCSS**

PROJECT LOMBOK **MICROSERVICE OPENSHIFT**

ANDROID MATERIAL DESIGN DAGGER 2 **RETROFIT RXJAVA**

SPRING KAFKA

MVP PRIMEFACES JSF STRUTS 2

MYECLIPSE JQUERY

JASPER **IREPORT** ORACLE DB MYSQL **INTELLIJ IDEA** JIRA **CONFLUENCE JENKINS GITHUB** Gitlab

SVN **ORACLE LINUX UBUNTU**

WEBLOGIC **TOMCAT GLASSFISH NETBEANS**

EDUCATION



Computer Science

Izmir University of Economics — 2006 - 2011

High School

Diyarbakır Ortadoğu High School — 2002 – 2005

Additional Education

BilgeAdam Academy (08.12.2014 - 23.01.2015)

- Java Server Faces & Primefaces (18 Hours)
- Spring Core Framework Training (24 Hours)
- Developing Web Application using JSF, Spring and Hibernate (30 Hours)
- Continuous Integration Using Maven Junit and Jenkins (12 hours)
- Hibernate Training (18 Hours)
- Java Development with Popular (latest or none) Agile Practices (12 Hours)

Kod Gemisi (7 – 11 August, 2017)

Microservice Architecture Training with Spring Cloud

PROJECTS

2021 – Sqassist – Auditor App

Ongoing project, based on making audits, getting results, analysis and chart for that audits. Technologies: Angular 11, TypeScript, Node.js, SOAP UI, Express.js, Bootstrap, Scss, Nestjs, MongoDB, mongoose.



2021 - The DAIMLER GROUP

I worked as a Frontend Developer in the software project that allows dynamically producing content for different countries in the showrooms of the Mercedes-Benz automotive company.

<u>Techonologies</u>: Angular 11, HTML 5, SCSS, PrimeNg, Karma, Jasmine, Java 8, Spring Boot, Spring Data JPA, Spring Kafka, Spring Core, Spring Security, Spring REST API, Jira, Github.

2020 - MARQUEZ Call Center Web Application - Telefónica | O2

Marquez call center application O2's customers can easily perform their transactions on GSM lines and DSL lines through the call center. In this process, customers' records and transactions can be made easily through the Marquez application.

<u>Techonologies</u>: Vue.js, HTML 5, Css, Vuetifyjs , Java, Spring Boot, Spring Rest API, Spring Rest Client, Typescript, Cypress, Bitbucket, Jira, SSO

2020 - Landwirt-direkt.de - Codenorm

The Landwirt web application is a web application that allows regional foods to be served online directly from the producer to the customer. In the application, there is a manufacturer interface that allows you to enter information about the products produced by the manufacturers, the detailed contents of the products and the delivery times. The customer interface of the application offers a user-friendly interface that allows different features such as order, online payment, delivery tracking on the map, comments about the product and the manufacturer.

<u>Techonologies</u>: Angular Universal (10), HTML, SCSS, Spring, Spring Boot, Kafka, ELK, Keycloack, Nginx, BDD, Git, Docker, Kubernetes, Jira, Slack

2019 - Friendship Web Application (https://www.u-dating.club)

The application was developed as a system of finding friends and sharing articles between people who live in Germany. Through the application, people can become friends. They can speak among themselves in writing, voice and video conferencing.

<u>Techonologies</u>: Angular 8, Angular Universal, HTML 5, SCSS, Bootstrap 4, Node.js, WebRTC, SendEffect API, Micropayment, Typescript, Docker, Jasmine, Karma, Socket.io, Gitlab, CometChat Pro, Digital Ocean, JavaScript, Nginx

2019 - Alo Sigorta Mobile App

Alo Insurance Mobile application offers users the opportunity to make traffic, insurance, earthquake and health insurance. Thanks to the application, users can enter the minimum information and reach the most discounted offers to perform the payment process.

Technologies: Angular 8, Ionic 4, TypeScript, Node.js, SOAP UI, Express.js, Scss

2019 – FUEL Analytics

The Fuel Analytics project is used to analyze the fuel data used by aircraft on lufthansa airlines. These datas is getting from Pyhton Project via Web Services. In this way, instant analysis data can be displayed in practice.

Technologies: Angular 8, Bootstrap 4, HTML 5, SCSS, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring REST, Spring Core, OpenShift, Spring Kafka, Gitlab, Jira, Confluence, Jenkins, Karma, E2E Test, Junit, Maven

2019 - Chronos

The application helps a company that serves construction companies in Germany to follow up all business processes and then generate reports to complete the official processes correctly. Then the company started to offer this application which was developed for itself as a solution to the companies operating in the European region.

<u>Techonologies</u>: Angular 7, Nrwl, HTML 5, SCSS, jsPDF, Docker, Java 8, Spring Framework, Spring Security, Spring Data JPA, Lombok Project, Spring Batch, Spring Data For MongoDB, Spring Kafka, Microservice Architecture, Spring Boot, Docker, Maven, Bitbucket, Jira, Confluence, Slack

2018 - Cornelsen (www.cornelsen.de) - Codenorm

The Cornelsen web application is a web project that enables customers to access their educational content quickly within the framework of certain legal powers and is completed using advanced technologies.

Technologies: Angular 8, Material Design, HTML 5, SCSS, Docker, Spring Boot, AWS, Spring Framework, Spring Security, ElasticSearch, Lombok Project, Maven, Gitlab, Jenkins, Confluence, Jira.

2018 - Individual-Society and Brand Relationship in Social Media

It is the basis of the research which is able to fix the product-consumer connection in the sense that every word on TV or radio is followed in Twitter. In addition to the consumer's brand relationship, daily, monthly and yearly interest and consumption trends can be determined and accordingly it is aimed to reach the consumer more clearly. In addition to standard measurements, the responses are measured by converting the audio data into text data and comparing it on huge databases.

Algorithms: Gesture, Levenstein, Fourier Transform etc.

<u>Techonologies</u>: TwitterAPI Stream Data, BigData / Hadoop HDSF, Docker, Gitlab, Linux, Java 8, Angular 2 + (Angular 2, 4, 5, 6, 7), Spring Boot, Microservices, etc.

CODENORM (Remote Java Full Stack Developer)

Germany — **2017**-

CLP GMBH – Logistic Project

It is ongoing project for our customer CLP GMBH. We have been implementing a logistic project with group of 3 people. I have been contributed all stages of the project.

<u>Technologies</u>: Vue.js, Angular 5, Spring-Boot, Java 8, Spring-Cloud, Apache Kafka, Microservice Architecture, Docker, Docker-Compose, Maven, Mockito, Junit, GIT, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, HTML 5, SCSS, Jasmine, Bootstrap 4, Angular-CLI, Nrwl

Cumolocity IoT-

IoT project with a partner. I had worked as a software engineer at that project. I had

responsibilities of writing drivers for communication between devices and wrote unit tests for this project.

Technologies: Spring -Boot, Java 8, Multithreading, JUnit, Mockito

Ergo Group - ITERGO

We had implemented a tax and expense management tool for Ergo Group Company.

<u>Technologies</u>: Angular 5, Spring-Boot, Java 8, Spring-Cloud, Apache Kafka, Microservice Architecture, Docker, Docker-Compose, Maven, Mockito, Junit, GIT, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, HTML 5, SCSS, Jasmine, Bootstrap 4, Angular-CLI, Nrwl, Kubernetes, Dokku

2018 - Biçen Law Firm Mobile Application



Biçen Law Firm mobile application is designed as a mobile application where people can ask opinions and suggestions to the lawyers. Users are able to follow what they are asking as a member via mobile application. In addition, users can make appointments from the attorneys for face-to-face meetings.

Techonologies: Ionic 3, Angular 5, TypeScript, Firebase, SCSS, HTML 5, GIT, Jira

<u>Apple Store URL: https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/biçen-avukatlık-bürosu/id1397816674?l=tr&ls=1&mt=8</u>

Google Play Store URL: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=tr.av.bicen



2016-2017 IT Service Desk Application



IT Service Desk application for recording all devices in the company and following their repairing process.

<u>Technologies</u>: Spring, Spring Boot, Angular 4, Spring Data JPA, Spring Security, Spring REST, Oracle DB, Jenkins, Jira, Project Lombok, HTML 5, Bootstrap 4, TypeScript, SCSS

2015 - Investment Tracking Application



Investment Tracking Application is about tracking of investment in company. Thanks to this application, the company can track the processes of the invesment department in detail and report the progress payment.

Technologies: JSF 2.2, Primefaces 5, Spring Framework, Hibernate, Spring Security, Maven, GIT, Weblogic, Oracle, Jenkins, Jira Software

2013 - Smartlis Laboratory Application





Laboratory Application for test results.

- Doctors send examples to the laboratory
- Read test results from the test devices
- Report test results of the example

Technologies: Struts 2, JQuery, Weblogic, Oracle 11g Video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zEX-Z4VqHWQ

2013 - Diski Android Mobile Application





Diski Mobile Application some modules :

- News , Projects, Departments, Pay Offices
- General Manager, Company Info
- Subscriber bill details
- Pay bill with credit card
- Take photo and send to help desk

Techologies: Android, Eclipse

Google Play: https://play.google.com/store/apps/developer?id=DiSKi

2009-2012 - DISKI Subsciber Information Management Software (DISKION2)





Software for Administrating Water and Sewage operations.

I was framework developer, ui developer and weblogic administrator.

Some capabilities of the software:

- Reads watermeters with casio hand terminals
- Calculate bills
- Billing payment by credit card, online, pay-office
- New subscipter apply process.
- Watermeters sell and repair
- Help desk

Techonologies: Struts 2, Jquery, JQGrid, JDBC,Oracle 11g, Weblogic, SVN, ESXi, Jasper Reports

DISKI

2013 - Bank Online Payment System

I am aware of needed every company interract with each other in today's technology. For these reason, I have completed developing system that communicate with 13 banks in order to increase payment point for the our subscribers.

Technologies: Java Restful-JAXRS, Oracle Database

LANGUAGES



Turkish: Native Language

English: Advanced Spanish: Basic

EXPERIENCE



JAVA FULL STACK DEVELOPER

İzmir, Turkey — 2017 – 2018

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, DISKI (Diyarbakir Water and Sewage Administration)

Diyarbakir, Turkey — 2011-2017

CO-FOUNDER, CEMSOFT